lacourt.org 2017-11-18

# LA Court

LA COURT 

Web Site Privacy Statement 

This policy explains how the Los Angeles Superior Court (LASC) treats information that its web site collects and receives, including information related to your past use of services provided on the web site and information about you that is personally identifiable.

User Tracking and Data Capture Practices

In general, the LASC web site collects and aggregates user information regarding use of our web sites and web pages for purposes of statistical and other analysis so as to help us improve our web sites. Among other things, LASC may collect and record domain names and/or IP addresses. This tells us what services are used by distinct users, but does not tell us the individual identities of the users.

In some areas of the LASC web site, in order for us to provide the specific services, we do require and record personally identifiable information. This is done with users’ active permission and participation.

On the Traffic Online Services pages and e-Filing, users are required to provide Name, Address, e-mail address and other personal information to enable us to complete the specific on-line transactions. To access the Index of Defendants in Criminal Cases and Civil Case Document Images, users are required to register with the LASC web site and create a user account. Users must provide information such as a User ID, Password, Name, Billing Address, Credit Card Type, Credit Card Number and Credit Card Expiration Date. After your account is created, this information will be used for verification when you access these services.

Once you register with the LASC web site and sign in, you are not anonymous to us. Only the minimal set of required information for processing credit card transactions is requested and stored. This information is necessary for payment processing and enables repeated users to access electronic court records. It will only be used for such purpose. No individually identifiable information will be employed in usage pattern reporting.

The LASC web site also uses "session-specific cookies" on the following pages in order to run its interactive online applications: Traffic Online Services, e-Filing, Index of Defendants in Criminal Cases, Calendars, Case Summaries and ADR Neutral Search. In the future, we may use cookies on other pages as well. A cookie is a small amount of data which often includes an anonymous unique identifier which is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. The data stored in these cookies is read by the LASC web site for the purposes stated above. You can set your web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. Some services and functionality on the LASC web site may be impaired if you decline to accept cookies.

Confidentiality and Data Security

We want our site visitors to feel confident about using the LASC web site and, therefore, are committed to protecting the information we collect.

Unless required by law, the Los Angeles Superior Court will not transfer, sell, or otherwise make available to third parties information about, related to, or provided by users of its web site, including email and mailing addresses.

We limit access to personal information about our users to those LASC employees for whom we believe such access to be appropriate in light of the functions and responsibilities of their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information that is stored in our systems from unauthorized access. Our systems are configured with full 128-bit SSL-based data encryption or scrambling technologies and with firewalls to help protect confidential information, such as names, addresses, credit card numbers, and passwords. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card number when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

It is crucial that, as a user, you protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer and that you always sign off when finished using a shared computer. Further, you should be aware that no system is impenetrable. Thus, it is your responsibility diligently to monitor your credit card statements, bank statements and similar personal information so as to discover and address as quickly as possible any misuse of your personal information. Neither LASC nor any other governmental agency, entity or body nor any vendor or service provider associated with any of our online efforts will be liable for any loss or damage relating to unauthorized access to your personal information on our system.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

The Los Angeles Superior Court may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site.

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, kindly contact:

Los Angeles Superior Court  
Webmaster  
Court Technology Services  
320 W. Temple St., Room G-25  
Los Angeles, CA 90012

webmaster@lacourt.org

Last Updated: May 19, 2005

Art Showcased in  
Los Angeles Courthouse Jury Rooms

"Flamingo Resort" by Michael Artis  
2009 – Amateur 3rd Place
